All of the exercises in this lesson are held in
这节课的所有练习都位于
the ML-case-studies Notebook we created earlier.
我们之前创建的 ML-case-studies Notebook 中
So I'm going to start this up and just open it in Jupyter.
在 Jupyter 中打开此 Notebook
I'll navigate to the Payment_Fraud_Detection directory
转到 Payment_Fraud_Detection 目录
and to the Fraud_Detection_Exercise Notebook.
并打开 Fraud_Detection_Exercise Notebook
To approach the task of fraud detection,
对于欺诈检测任务
we'll be looking at credit card data that was initially taken from Kaggle.
我们将查看来自 Kaggle 的信用卡数据
This data includes thousands of transactions with
这个数据集包含成千上万的交易条目
anonymized features and class labels, fraudulent or valid.
其中包含匿名特征和类别标签“欺诈性”或“有效性”
We'll follow a typical machine learning workflow.
我们将遵循典型的机器学习工作流程
Loading in and exploring our data,
首先加载和探索数据
then moving onto splitting that data and parsing it to a binary classification model.
然后拆分数据并传递给二元分类模型
In this notebook, we'll start with training and deploying
在此 notebook 中 我们首先将使用 SageMaker 的
a built-in linear model using SageMaker's LinearLearner.
LinearLearner 训练和部署内置线性模型
We'll also discuss the unique challenges that fraud detection
我们还会讨论欺诈检测面临的独特挑战性
has such as imbalanced training data,
例如训练数据不平衡
that is a history of more valid transactions than fraudulent ones.
即有效交易的历史记录比欺诈性交易的要多
A lot of this Notebook will be about taking a model
这个 Notebook 的很大一部分内容是讨论
and improving it based on data or design challenges.
如何根据数据或设计挑战改进模型
As we go, we'll evaluate the models we trained by
并且我们将通过各种指标
looking at a variety of metrics for success,
评估训练的模型
not just accuracy, but precision and recall as well. All right.
这些指标不仅包括准确率 还有精确率和召回率好的
So in the first cell, I'm loading in my usual resources,
在第一个单元格中正常加载资源
and in the next, I'm just storing my SageMaker variables.
在下个单元格中设置 SageMaker 变量
So that's the SageMaker session enroll which will help me
包括 SageMaker 会话和角色
define how we train our models and a default bucket.
这些变量定义了模型的训练方式和默认存储桶
The S3 bucket is where we'll store
我们将在 S3 存储桶里
our training data as well as any saved model parameters.
存储训练数据以及保存的模型参数
After getting my SageMaker resources,
获得 SageMaker 资源后
I'm going to actually load in our data from online.
从网上加载数据
This link will get me a credit card fraud.zip file which I'll unzip here.
从这个链接可以下载 creditcardfraud.zip 文件 解压缩该文件
You only need to run the cell once and you'll get a credit card.csv file.
只需运行这个单元格一次 即可获得 creditcard.csv 文件
Then, I'm going to read that data in as a dataframe and print out the shape of our data.
然后将数据读取为 dataframe 并输出数据的形状
I can see I have about 285 thousand data points.
可以看到 我们有约 28.5 万个数据点
If I look at the first few rows,
从前几行数据可以看到
I can see the features that this includes.
这些数据包含的特征
It includes the time of transaction,
包括从第一个交易开始的
since the first transaction,
交易时间
and a number of anonymized features V1 through V28.
以及从 V1 到 V28 的匿名特征
Then, it has the amount of the transaction and a class label at the very end.
最后是交易额和类别标签
So overall, I have 30 input features and a single class.
总体来说 有 30 个输入特征和一个类别
Zero indicates valid, which all of these points are,
0 表示有效 所有这些数据点都是有效交易
and one will indicate a fraudulent transaction.
1 表示欺诈性交易
Now, you can't learn much from these anonymized features,
这些匿名特征并不能提供太多信息
but you can look at how the data is distributed over each of our classes.
但是可以查看每个类别的数据分布情况
So your first task will be to complete this function, fraudulent percentage.
你的第一个任务是完成函数 fraudulent_percentage
This function takes in the transaction dataframe that we just loaded
这个函数的参数是刚刚加载的 transaction_df
in and it should return the percentage of the data that's labeled as fraudulent.
它应该返回标为欺诈性的数据所占百分比
Below, I've given you a test cell to test
我在下面提供了测试单元格
out an implementation of this function when you complete it.
当你实现完这个函数后 可以测试一下
Now, the next step will be to ingest this data and use it to train our model.
下一步是使用这些数据训练模型
With that goal in mind,
知道目标后
I'm going to give you the second task,
再布置第二个任务
splitting these data into training and test sets.
请将这些数据划分为训练集和测试集
That is completing this function: train, test, split.
即完成函数 train_test_split
This, again, takes in our transaction dataframe
这个函数的参数也包括 transaction_df
and a fraction of that data to withhold for training.
第二个参数是训练数据的比例
The rest should be held for testing.
剩下的是测试数据
So this default value of 0.7 means
默认值 0.7 表示
that 70 percent of our data should be kept for training,
70% 用作训练数据
and then 30 percent should go to test data.
30% 用作测试数据
So try to both calculate the percentage of data that's
请计算欺诈性数据的百分比
fraudulent and complete this function to split the data.
然后完成此函数以拆分数据
I've left some guidelines in this Notebook,
我在 Notebook 中提供了一些指导说明
but if you get stuck or you want to check your solution,
如果你遇到问题或者想要检查你的代码
I'll go over my solution next.
请观看下个解答视频